simplenichestrategies.com 2012-05-23

# Simple Silo Site Privacy Policy

### This is the Privacy Policy for Simple Silo Plugins And Associated Products

At Simple Silo, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit our sites, and how we safeguard your information. We **never** sell your personal information to third parties.

### Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site(s) and which pages you visited throughout our site(s).

### Cookies and Web Beacons

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site(s). This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as our forums and member areas.

We may also use third party advertisements on simplesilo.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.

### DoubleClick DART cookies

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting <http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx>

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

### Joining our site(s) and downloading plugins

If you register to join the site(s) in order to download a plugins, articles or manuscripts we will securely store any details that you provide us with in our databases. We will not share this information with any third party. We may from time to time contact you regarding new plugins and/or policy changes at simplesilo.com, this will be done via email and unsubscription information will be provided with each email.
